{
  "vocabularyquestions": [
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank: I ______ down for an hour every afternoon.",
      "answer1": "A) lied",
      "answer2": "B) lye",
      "answer3": "C) lie",
      "answer4": "D) lay",
      "correct": "D) lay"
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct statement:",
      "answer1": "A) Please turn on the light.",
      "answer2": "B) Please shut the light.",
      "answer3": "C) Please open the light.",
      "answer4": "D) Please shut down the light.",
      "correct": "A) Please turn on the light."
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct statement:",
      "answer1": "A) I had a strange dream last night.",
      "answer2": "B) I got a strange dream last night.",
      "answer3": "C) I saw a strange dream last night.",
      "answer4": "D) I faced a strange dream last night.",
      "correct": "A) I had a strange dream last night."
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct statement:",
      "answer1": "A) He tore the letter in anger.",
      "answer2": "B) He teared up the letter in anger.",
      "answer3": "C) He tore up the letter in anger.",
      "answer4": "D) He teared the letter in anger.",
      "correct": "C) He tore up the letter in anger."
    },
    {
      "question": "When a word ends with \"y\", and the letter before \"y\" is a consonant; for the various other forms of the word, \"y\" is replaced with:",
      "answer1": "A) ie",
      "answer2": "B) Oi",
      "answer3": "C) eng",
      "answer4": "D) e",
      "correct": "A) ie"
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct statement:",
      "answer1": "A) It is dirty, give it away.",
      "answer2": "B) It is dirty, throw it.",
      "answer3": "C) It is dirty, throw it away.",
      "answer4": "D) It is dirty, give it.",
      "correct": "C) It is dirty, throw it away."
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these words is correct?",
      "answer1": "A) Bereau",
      "answer2": "B) Beaurau",
      "answer3": "C) Bureau",
      "answer4": "D) Bureu",
      "correct": "C) Bureau"
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct statement:",
      "answer1": "A) I should take more exercise.",
      "answer2": "B) I should have more exercise.",
      "answer3": "C) I should make more exercise.",
      "answer4": "D) I should give more exercise.",
      "correct": "A) I should take more exercise."
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank: My watch is five minutes ______.",
      "answer1": "A) slow",
      "answer2": "B) early",
      "answer3": "C) before",
      "answer4": "D) behind",
      "correct": "D) behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank: The thief has ______ all my belongings.",
      "answer1": "A) robbed",
      "answer2": "B) taken",
      "answer3": "C) stolen",
      "answer4": "D) taken away",
      "correct": "C) stolen"
    }
  ]
}